

CONTACT



+34 644 719 786



mburguerat@gmail.com



C/ Aribau 225, 08021. Barcelona



<u>Portfolio</u>



<u>Github</u>



Linkedin

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- PYTHON
- MYSQL Workbench

LANGUAGES

- Catalan | Native
- Spanish | Native
- English | Intermediate
- French | Intermediate

MIQUEL BURGUERA

Despite being in the early stages of my career in the ASIX world, I have always been a sponge for information, soaking up knowledge and experience at every opportunity. In particular, I have discovered a passion for cybersecurity and other areas of ASIX that has further motivated me in my educational and professional journey. My focus on ASIX as a whole has allowed me to gain extensive knowledge in fields such as system administration, cybersecurity, network management, and more. While I am still in the process of learning, I am more motivated than ever after finding my true calling. I am committed to continued growth and making a positive contribution to any project or team I am part of.

EDUCATION

ADMINISTRATION OF COMPUTER SYSTEMS IN NETWORKS WITH CYBERSECURITY

IFP Barcelona, Spain

September 2023 - Current

ARCHITECTURE

Escuela Técnica Superior de Arquitectura de Barcelona (ETSAB) - UPC

2021 - 2023 (unfinished)

TECHNOLOGICAL BACHELOR'S DEGREE

Instituto Menéndez y Pelayo, Barcelona, Spain

2019 - 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

BISTRO RESTAURANT

Mallorca, Spain

Summers 2019 - 2020

Waiter

ES CANI RESTAURANT

Mallorca, Spain

Summers 2021 - 2022

Waiter